<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gradient Zero on Gradient Zero - Maschinelles Lernen für Unternehmen</title>
    <link>/de/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gradient Zero on Gradient Zero - Maschinelles Lernen für Unternehmen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 08:10:04 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Zero</title>
      <link>/de/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 08:10:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/de/projects/</guid>
      <description>Enterprise Machine Learning Learn more about our projects and research     &amp;nbsp;     Selected Projects AI Education In this project and in collaboration with scientific partners we will develop logic and digital exit games and the educational concept for their use in STEM education for children.
Digital Logic and Exit games are highly motivating, offer strong incentives to communicate and to collaborate, and encourage problem solving skills in a playful way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Zero - Aucom</title>
      <link>/de/aucom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 08:10:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/de/aucom/</guid>
      <description>Automated Unified Client Onboarding and Monitoring for Financial Institutions AUCOM     &amp;nbsp;     KYC as key requirement for financial institutions  Every financial institution must thoroughly screen its customers. They must screen them in advance and carefully monitor them afterwards. Through client due diligence the client is identified (are you who you say you are?) and screened (can you pose a risk?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Zero - Contact</title>
      <link>/de/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 08:10:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/de/contact/</guid>
      <description>   Kontakt Gradient Zero SoftwareentwicklungsGmbH Seilerstätte 22 / 1 / 3 1010 Wien, Österreich FN 503267 z. Handelsgericht Wien, UID: ATU73962946 E-Mail: office@gradient0.com     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Zero - Contact</title>
      <link>/de/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 08:10:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/de/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Datenschutz auf einen Blick Allgemeine Hinweise Die folgenden Hinweise geben einen einfachen Überblick darüber, was mit Ihren personenbezogenen Daten passiert, wenn Sie diese Website besuchen.  Personenbezogene Daten sind alle Daten, mit denen Sie persönlich identifiziert werden können. Ausführliche Informationen zum Thema Datenschutz entnehmen Sie unserer unter diesem Text aufgeführten Datenschutzerklärung.  Datenerfassung auf dieser Website Wer ist verantwortlich für die Datenerfassung auf dieser Website? Die Datenverarbeitung auf dieser Website erfolgt durch den Websitebetreiber.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
